A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 2, Series 3 FA461
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Finance Committee, 4
  - Meetings, 2
    - 1982 May 24, 26-27 (Box 50, Folder 314)
    - 1982 July 13 (Box 50, Folder 315)
    - JMB I, 1982 July 28 (Box 50, Folder 316)
    - 1982 Oct. 27, 29 (Box 50, Folder 317)
    - 1982 Oct. 27, 29 (Box 50, Folder 318)
    - 1982 Nov. 9 (Box 51, Folder 319)
    - Portfolio Activity Report - Fourth Quarter 1982, 1983 Feb. 17 (Box 51, Folder 320)
    - Portfolio Activity Report - Fourth Quarter 1983, 1984 Feb. 24 (Box 51, Folder 321)
    - 1984 April 10 (Box 51, Folder 322)
    - Portfolio Activity March 30, 1984 - Mailing to Board for Meeting, 1984 April 10 (Box 51, Folder 323)
    - 1984 May 7-8 (Box 51, Folder 324)
    - 1984 May 7-8 (Box 52, Folder 325)
    - Portfolio Report - May, 1984 June 9 (Box 52, Folder 326)
    - Portfolio Activity Report - First Quarter 1984, 1984 June 30 (Box 52, Folder 327)
    - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Repport, 1984 July 10 (Box 52, Folder 328)
    - Portfolio Update - End of August, 1984 Sept. 10 (Box 52, Folder 329)
    - Portfolio Activity Report - Second Quarter 1984, 1984 Sept. 14 (Box 52, Folder 330)
    - Portfolio Activity Report - Third Quarter, 1984 Sept. 30 (Box 52, Folder 331)
    - 1984 November 1 and 5 (Box 53, Folder 332)
    - 1984 November 1 and 5 (Box 53, Folder 333)
    - 1984 (Box 53, Folder 334)
    - 1984 November 13 (Box 53, Folder 335)
    - Finance Committee and Treasurer Report, 1984 Nov. 13 (Box 53, Folder 336)
    - Portfolio Activity Report - Third Quarter, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 337)
    - Portfolio Activity Report - Fourth Quarter, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 338)
    - Portfolio Activity Report - First Quarter, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 339)
    - Portfolio Activity Report - Second Quarter, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 340)
    - 1987 Jan. 28 (Box 54, Folder 341)
    - 1987 Jan. 28 (Box 54, Folder 342)
    - Portfolio Activity Report - Fourth Quarter 1986, 1987 March 31 (Box 54, Folder 343)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1987 April 14 (Box 54, Folder 344, Box 55, Folder 345)
    - 1987 June 1 (Box 55, Folder 346)
    - 1987 June 24 (Box 55, Folder 347)
    - 1987 June 24 (Box 55, Folder 348)
    - Portfolio Activity Report, 1987 June 30 (Box 55, Folder 349)
    - 1987 July 14 (Box 56, Folder 350)
    - 1987 Oct. 19 (Box 56, Folder 351)
    - Portfolio Activity Report - Third Quarter, 1987 Oct. 30 (Box 56, Folder 352)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1987 Nov. 10 (Box 56, Folder 353-354)
    - 1987 Dec. 7-8 (Box 56, Folder 355)
    - 1987 Dec. 7-8 (Box 57, Folder 356)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1988 July 12 (Box 57, Folder 357-358)
    - Letter to Finance Committee - re: Property Capital Trust, 1988 Sept. 7 (Box 57, Folder 359)
    - Accel Partners, 1988 Sept. 30 (Box 57, Folder 360)
    - 1988 Nov. 8 (Box 57, Folder 361)
    - 1988 Nov. 8 (Box 57, Folder 362)
    - Portfolio Activity Report, 1988 Nov. 8 (Box 58, Folder 363)
    - 1988 Dec. 13-14 (Box 58, Folder 364)
    - 1988 Dec. 13-14 (Box 58, Folder 365)
    - 1988 Dec. 13-14 (Box 58, Folder 366)
    - 1988 Dec. 13-14 (Box 58, Folder 367)
    - Correspondence, 1988 Dec. 21 (Box 58, Folder 368)
    - 1989 Jan. 31 (Box 58, Folder 369)
    - 1989 Jan. 31 (Box 59, Folder 370)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1989 April 11 (Box 59, Folder 371)
    - 1980 June 1-2 (Box 59, Folder 372)
    - 1989 June 1-2 (Box 59, Folder 373)
    - 1989 June 1-2 (Box 60, Folder 374)
    - Finance Report, 1989 June 30 (Box 60, Folder 375)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1989 July 11 (Box 60, Folder 376)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1989 Nov. 14 (Box 60, Folder 377)
    - 1989 November 30-December 1 (Box 60, Folder 378)
    - 1990 April 10 (Box 60, Folder 379)
  - Minutes, 3
    - 1919-1946 (Box 61, Folder 380)
    - 1931-1941 (Box 61, Folder 381)
    - 1931-1941 (Box 61, Folder 382)
    - 1941-1948 (Box 62, Folder 383)
    - 1948-1951 (Box 62, Folder 384)
    - 1951-1955 (Box 62, Folder 385)
    - 1951-1955 (Box 63, Folder 386)